Class of 1974 Records, 1970-[ongoing]
Smith College Archives
Class of 1974 Records
1970-[ongoing]
Smith College. Class of 1974
RG 80 UUID:5057212b-5142-4f46-bb8e-ddc783a0e387
2 boxes (.63 linear ft.)
Smith College Archives Northampton, MA
This collection contains photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, and other memorabilia from the commencement and reunions of the Class of 1974.
The Class of 1974 was the ninety-sixth graduating class of Smith College.
The Class of 1974 Records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1974, including materials from commencement, reunions, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, programs, letters, and other memorabilia.
Individual biographical files are also available, and often include photographs, photo albums, newspaper clippings, letters and correspondences, and class notes.
The records are open for research according to the regulations of the Smith College Archives without any additional restrictions.
The Class of 1974 Records were created by the students and donated to the College Archives.
- Commencement 1974 (Box 2258, Folder 1)
- Commencement Speaker 1974 (Box 2258, Folder 2)
- Freshman Handbook 1970-1971 (Box 2258, Folder 3)
- Groups 1974 (Box 2258, Folder 4)
- History 1970 (Box 2258, Folder 5)
- Ivy Day 1974 (Box 2258, Folder 6)
- Last Chapel 1974 (Box 2258, Folder 7)
- Class Letters 1974-1976 (Box 2258, Folder 8)
- Reunions 1979-1984 (Box 2258, Folder 9)
- Reunions 1989 (Box 2258, Folder 10)
- Reunions 1999 (Box 2258, Folder 11)
- Reunions 2004 (Box 2258, Folder 12)
- Who's Who 1970 (Box 2258, Folder 13)